(this["webpackJsonpturin-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpturin-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{11:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var s=n(1),i=n.n(s),o=n(4),r=n.n(o),a=(n(9),n(2)),c=n.p+"static/media/click.a8760bf5.mp3",u=n(0);function l(){var e=Object(s.useState)(0),t=Object(a.a)(e,2),n=t[0],i=t[1],o=Object(s.useState)(!1),r=Object(a.a)(o,2),l=r[0],h=r[1],j=Object(s.useState)(0),x=Object(a.a)(j,2),b=x[0],d=x[1],p=[{questionText:"In which part of Italy Turin is located?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Northern Italy.",points:1},{answerText:"Center of Italy.",points:0},{answerText:"Southern Italy.",points:0}]},{questionText:"How many inhabitants does Turin have?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"More than a million.",points:0},{answerText:"Between 500k and one million.",points:1},{answerText:"Less than 500k.",points:0}]},{questionText:"Which of these monuments is the symbol of Turin?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Sforzesco Castle.",points:0},{answerText:"The Pantheon.",points:0},{answerText:"Mole Antonelliana.",points:1}]},{questionText:"Which of these museums can you visit in Turin?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Wax Museum.",points:0},{answerText:"Cinema Museum.",points:1},{answerText:"Pinacoteca di Brera.",points:0}]},{questionText:"Which of these football teams is from Turin?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Inter.",points:0},{answerText:"Juventus.",points:1},{answerText:"Atalanta.",points:0}]},{questionText:"Which of these car manufacturers was founded in Turin?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Fiat.",points:1},{answerText:"Ferrari.",points:0},{answerText:"Dacia.",points:0}]},{questionText:"Which of these Nobel Prizes was born in Turin?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Enrico Fermi.",points:0},{answerText:"Dario Fo.",points:0},{answerText:"Rita Levi-Montalcini.",points:1}]},{questionText:"Which of these traditional foods is typical in Turin?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Bagna cauda.",points:1},{answerText:"Parmigiana.",points:0},{answerText:"Pasta alla carbonara.",points:0}]},{questionText:"In which year was Turin declared the capital of Italy?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"1848.",points:0},{answerText:"1861.",points:1},{answerText:"Never.",points:0}]},{questionText:"Which mountains frame Turin?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"The Apennines.",points:0},{answerText:"The Alps.",points:1},{answerText:"The Pyrenees.",points:0}]}];function w(){new Audio(c).play(),i(0),d(0),h(!1)}return l&&b>7?Object(u.jsxs)(u.Fragment,{children:[Object(u.jsx)("h1",{children:"QUIZ"}),Object(u.jsx)("h2",{children:"Do you know Turin?"}),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"app",children:[Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:["Your score is: ",Object(u.jsx)("br",{})," ",b," out of ",p.length,". ",Object(u.jsx)("br",{}),Object(u.jsx)("br",{}),"Congratulations, you know Turin very well!"]}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{className:"button-reset",onClick:function(){return w()},children:"Restart"})]}),Object(u.jsx)("footer",{children:"Made with \u2764\ufe0f by Andrea Bruno"})]}):l&&b>=5&&b<=7?Object(u.jsxs)(u.Fragment,{children:[Object(u.jsx)("h1",{children:"QUIZ"}),Object(u.jsx)("h2",{children:"Do you know Turin?"}),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"app",children:[Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:["Your score is: ",Object(u.jsx)("br",{}),b," out of ",p.length,". ",Object(u.jsx)("br",{}),Object(u.jsx)("br",{}),"Not bad! You should come here to find out more!"]}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{className:"button-reset",onClick:function(){return w()},children:"Restart"})]}),Object(u.jsx)("footer",{children:"Made with \u2764\ufe0f by Andrea Bruno"})]}):l&&b<5?Object(u.jsxs)(u.Fragment,{children:[Object(u.jsx)("h1",{children:"QUIZ"}),Object(u.jsx)("h2",{children:"Do you know Turin?"}),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"app",children:[Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:["Your score is: ",Object(u.jsx)("br",{})," ",b," out of ",p.length,". ",Object(u.jsx)("br",{}),Object(u.jsx)("br",{}),"You should definitely come and visit Turin!"]}),Object(u.jsx)("button",{className:"button-reset",onClick:function(){return w()},children:"Ricomincia"})]}),Object(u.jsx)("footer",{children:"Made with \u2764\ufe0f by Andrea Bruno"})]}):Object(u.jsxs)(u.Fragment,{children:[Object(u.jsx)("h1",{children:"QUIZ"}),Object(u.jsx)("h2",{children:"Do you know Turin?"}),Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"app",children:[Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(u.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(u.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",n+1]}),"/",p.length]}),Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:p[n].questionText})]}),Object(u.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:p[n].answerOptions.map((function(e,t){return Object(u.jsx)("button",{className:"button-answer",onClick:function(){return function(e){new Audio(c).play(),e&&d(b+e);var t=n+1;t<p.length?i(t):h(!0)}(e.points)},children:e.answerText})}))})]}),Object(u.jsx)("footer",{children:"Made with \u2764\ufe0f by Andrea Bruno"})]})}r.a.render(Object(u.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(u.jsx)(l,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))},9:function(e,t,n){}},[[11,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.7da5b659.chunk.js.map